So we want to hear from you guys, so please call us up, 1-855-AMANDA-8.
So this brother, Marquise White, a teacher who gained attention on TikTok for allowing students to paint his nails and do his hair in the classroom, has been fired.
Marquise had a hair appointment after school, so he asked some of his students to take down his braids at the end of the day and then posted the video on TikTok.
And while many commenters supported the teacher's behavior, some expressed concerns about its appropriateness, especially regarding boundaries between students and teachers.
So as a parent, let's start with you.
First, I was like, this is a little weird, him doing that with all these little girls in the classroom.
But then I looked at it, they weren't doing anything sexualized in nature, and it seemed to be all innocent fun.
I'm in the middle of the whole thing because it did look kind of strange, but his reasoning for it sounded like it was okay.
And the parents are good with it, so you just have to be a good judge of character.
For me, there's a cultural context to this that I think is unique, even though I did see a lot of Black people that felt like this was inappropriate.
Teachers spend so much time with kids.
I do think that there is a certain level of familiarity that can be fostered that is necessary for them to be a safe space.
I think that that does end up being a bit of a dance.
For me, I just felt like when I watched it, it didn't seem unseemly to me.
It just felt more like culturally, contextually, like, it just felt like a Black people thing.
Yeah, it did.
It did, it did.
It did.
We are...